smesauda.com 2016-03-15

# SME Sauda

This Privacy Policy explains how Smesauda collects, uses, discloses and protects your Personal Information, obtained explicitly through www.smesauda.com website ("Site"), as well as other information collected automatically without direct submission by you. 

**Scope**   
The terms of the Privacy Policy provided herein govern your use of Smesauda Website and the information accessible on or from this Website. The Privacy Policy also lays down how smesauda may collect, use and share any information provided by you. BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. 

Smesauda reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Smesauda recommends that you revisit this privacy policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of the current privacy practices. 

**Mandatory information**   
Depending upon the activity, some of the information that Smesauda may ask you to provide will be identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. Similarly, if you wish to delete your information that is mandatory, you will no longer be able to engage in that particular activity. Mandatory information is applicable for. 

**What personal information Smesauda collects**   
Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact an individual. When you register with the website and create a Smesauda ID, avail of the services provided by Smesauda, upload any content on the website, Smesauda may collect a variety of personal Information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact number,etc. 

Your personal information will be kept confidential to the maximum possible extent and used to support your relationship with Smesauda, to notify you of the various offers, updated information and new software applications and other related functions from Smesauda.

By using this website and the products and services provided on the website, You agree and acknowledge that Your Personal Information collected through the website may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any country around the world. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted third party vendors or agents of Smesauda such as credit card processors, web hosting providers, communication services, and web analytic providers, to help facilitate Smesauda in providing certain functions. 

**How Smesauda uses your personal information**   
Smesauda collects your information in order to record, support and facilitate your participation in the services provided by Smesauda and to prevent fraud and unlawful use. As provided earlier, Your Personal Information may also be used to track customer preferences to provide a customized Website experience and keep you informed about product/service upgrades, new vendors additions in categories of your interest, special offers and other products and services of Smesauda and its third party providers unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law. 

Smesauda may use personal information to verify whether you are entitled to access and use the Website and the products and services available on the Website. This personal information may also be used to enable Smesauda to enhance the experience and user friendliness of your website visit, to assist you with customer service or technical support issues, or to follow up with you after your visit, or to otherwise support your relationship with Smesauda. 

Smesauda does not rent, sell or share your personal information with third parties or non-affiliated companies except to provide the services you have requested. Smesauda limits the disclosure of personal information to smesauda employees, independent contractors including vendors, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers and distributors of Smesauda Services, on a need-to-know basis, and only if the disclosure will enable that entity to provide Smesauda with business, professional, or technical support or fulfill your request. 

Thus, the Personal Information provided by you is used only:   
• To facilitate your use of the website  
• To respond to your inquiries or fulfill your requests for information about the various services  
• To connect you with the vendors and their authorised dealers, in order to facilitate the purchase of your desired products  
• To provide you with information about Smesauda's services and the vendor products offered on the Website and to send you Information, materials, and offers from Smesauda  
• To provide you with important information regarding the Website, changes to Smesauda's terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information  
• To send you marketing communications that Smesauda believes may be of interest to you.  
• To personalize your experience on the website and Smesauda's other websites by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to your requirements  
• To help you address your problems with the website  
• To assist you/your company in accessing discounted offers for your desired products/services and to assist in completion of sale of the products/services by the authorised dealer to you and to provide you with related customer service  
• For proper administering of the website  
• To conduct internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website)  
• To improve the services, content and advertising on the Website  
• To protect the integrity of the Website  
• To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law

**What non-personal information Smesauda collects**   
Non-Personal Information is any information that does not reveal your specific identity, such as, browser information, information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, demographic information, etc. 

As evident with most websites, the Website (www.smesauda.com) gathers some information automatically when you visit the URL of the Website and stores it in log files. When you use the Website and the services provided on the Website, Smesauda may collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use of the Website, and the products and the services available on the Website. 

**How Smesauda uses your non-personal information**   
With respect to Non-Personal Information automatically collected and stored in log files, Smesauda uses this information to understand and analyse trends, to administer the Website, to learn about user behaviour on the Website, and to gather demographic information about the user base as a whole. Smesauda may use this information in its marketing and advertising services. Smesauda also uses such information to measure traffic patterns on the Website and usage of the products and services. 

As Non-Personal Information does not personally identify you, Smesauda may use and disclose Non-Personal Information for any purpose. In some instances, Smesauda may combine Non-Personal Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographical location). If Smesauda combines any Non-Personal Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

**To whom Smesauda may disclose your personal information**   
Your Personal Information may be disclosed-

• To Smesauda's affiliates, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy  
• To Smesauda's third party providers who provide goods/services such as contact information verification, payment processing, order fulfillment, collection of payments, customer service, website hosting, data analysis, infrastructure provision, IT services, auditing services and other similar services to enable them to provide the services  
• If you request information from vendors so that they can provide you with information about their products and services. Smesauda SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR VENDORS' USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
• If you so request, information may be disclosed to third parties to permit them to send you marketing communications, including third parties who may provide similar services as the original service about which you requested more information  
• To third party sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions  
• By you, services on which you are able to post information and materials. Please note that any information you post or disclose through these services will become public information, and may be available to visitors to the Website and to the general public  
• To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings)  
• As Smesauda may believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce Smesauda’s terms of use; (e) to protect Smesauda’s operations or those of any of Smesauda’s affiliates; (f) to protect Smesauda’s rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of Smesauda’s affiliates, You or others; and (g) to allow Smesauda to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that Smesauda may sustain

**Protection of personal information**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of such Personal Information, Smesauda has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Personal Information collected online.

**Access to personal information**   
You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at www.smesauda.com. For other Personal Information, Smesauda makes good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that Smesauda correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Smesauda is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. Smesauda may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.

**Third party links**   
This Website contains links to other websites operated by third parties that are not controlled by, or affiliated or associated with Smesauda. Accordingly,Smesauda does not make any representations concerning the privacy practices or policies of such third parties or terms of use of such websites, nor does Smesauda control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, messages or other materials available on such websites. The inclusion or exclusion does not imply any endorsement by Smesauda of the website, the website's provider, or the information on the website. The third party websites may also have privacy policies that differ from this Privacy Policy. It is recommended that you review the privacy policy on any such websites prior to using such websites.

**Cookies**   
Smesauda's website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help Smesauda better understand user behaviour, tell Smesauda which parts of the Smesauda website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Smesauda treats information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, Smesauda also treats these identifiers as personal information.

The cookies are installed by Smesauda exclusively for the purpose of retrieving information from you for the purpose of analysing trends, statistics and in the process, providing better customer service. While Smesauda uses cookies and similar devices to track your use of the Website and the products and services (such as the types of products purchased and services used, how many users Smesauda receive daily, the Website pages visited), and web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, Smesauda does not generally use this information to identify you personally. However, there may be exceptions to this. If you expressly provide consent for the Website to remember the unique identifier that you select when you register for various activities on the Website, that unique identifier will be stored on a persistent cookie on your computer and that unique identifier will be linked to your registration information. As a result, your navigation path around the Website will be tracked in identifiable form. 

Smesauda may, if you so choose, send direct advertisement mailers to you at the address given by you. You have the option to opt-out of this direct mailer by way of links provided at the bottom of each mailer. We respect your privacy and in the event that you choose not to receive such mailers, Smesauda will take all steps to remove you from the list.

**Contact us**   
If You have questions or concerns about Smesauda’s Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact Smesauda at 

**SMB Unisol Pvt. Ltd.**  
198/30, Second Floor  
Ramesh Market, East of Kailash  
New Delhi-110065 INDIA 

Email: [support@smesauda.com](mailto:support@smesauda.com)
